<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book on Yunyi&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.yunyitang.me/zh/tags/book/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book on Yunyi&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.yunyitang.me/zh/tags/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>十一月在读</title>
      <link>https://www.yunyitang.me/zh/blog/life/nov-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.yunyitang.me/zh/blog/life/nov-book/</guid>
      <description>YUNYI IS CURRENTLY READING The Body Keeps the Score Mind, Brain and Body in the Transformation of Trauma by Bessel van der Kolk 冬牧场 作者：李娟, Jack Hargreaves (Translator), and Yan Yan (Translator) &amp;lsquo;Encouraged by her neighbors, Li decides to join a family of Kazakh herders as they take their 30 boisterous camels, 500 sheep, and over 100 cattle and horses to pasture for</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p><a href="https://www.goodreads.com/review/list/161105203-yunyi-tang?shelf=currently-reading" target="_blank" rel="noopener" style="color:#E16723";>YUNYI IS CURRENTLY READING</a></p>
</blockquote>
<h1 id="the-body-keeps-the-score">The Body Keeps the Score</h1>
<blockquote>
<p>Mind, Brain and Body in the Transformation of Trauma</p>
</blockquote>
<p>by Bessel van der Kolk</p>
<h1 id="冬牧场">冬牧场</h1>
<p>作者：李娟, Jack Hargreaves (Translator), and Yan Yan (Translator)</p>
<p>&lsquo;Encouraged by her neighbors, Li decides to join a family of Kazakh herders as they take their 30 boisterous camels, 500 sheep, and over 100 cattle and horses to pasture for the winter.&rsquo; It&rsquo;s a cold lonely journey but also a warm family journey into the freezing-cold Kazakh winter pasture. It&rsquo;s amazing that her words bring me so vividly into the unfamiliar Kazakh land in a cold winter in the hot summer when I first finished reading it, and I feel eager to reread it in an actually cold winter now. Her words are like snow, seemingly weightless, but silently nourishing the earth. Life and talent have given Juan a unique sense of perception of the Kazakh world.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
